Guide to the Records of the Deputy/Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Eleazor Bromberg 1952-1980 RG 6.1 RG 6.1
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of Deputy/Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs (Eleazor Bromberg)
1952-1980
RG 6.1
New York University Archives
42.0 linear feet 42 linear feet (42 boxes)
This collection contains the records of Eleazor Bromberg, applied mathematician and NYU administrator, during his tenure as Deputy/Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs.
Bromberg, Eleazor
Arrangement
Folders are arranged topically.
The files are grouped into one series:
I, Topical Files
Physical Access
Please note that this collection is stored offsite, and you must contact the repository to schedule access.
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains correspondence, reports, memoranda, and other materials related to Bromberg's role as Deputy/Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs.
Historical/Biographical Note
Eleazor Bromberg, applied mathematician and NYU administrator, began his career at NYU in 1953 at the Courant Institute of Mathematical Studies. He started as the Administrative Director of the Atomic Energy Commission's Computing Center. In 1957 he became the Administrative Manager of Courant and in 1959 the Assistant Director. He also served as Associate Professor of Applied Mathematics and Theoretical Mechanics from 1953 to 1957 and became a full Professor of Applied Mathematics in 1957.
In 1970 Bromberg joined the central administration as Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs. In this capacity he assisted in planning and administering the University's instructional, research, and public service programs. He succeeded Dr. David Z. Robinson.
In 1972 Bromberg was named Deputy Chancellor of the University.
Bromberg was born October 7, 1913 in Toronto, Canada. He received a Bachelor of Science degree from the City College of New York in 1933, a Master of Arts in Physics from Columbia University in 1935, and his Ph.D. in Applied Mathematics from NYU in 1950. In 1948 he married Edith Weiss, with whom he had three sons.
Sources:
Bromberg, Eleazor, Biographical File, NYU Archives.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files included in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted.
Provenance
This collection was tranferred to the University Archives in 1989.
Bromberg, Eleazor; New York University.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Memorandums.; Minutes.; New York (State) |z New York.; New York University |x Administration.; New York University. Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences.; Reports.
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Report, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Barcode #: 3 1142 042262983
  - Statement of Current Revenues, ca.1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226298 3
  - Statement of Current Revenues, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Science Education, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - GBA Targets Conference, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Government Regulations, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Advisory Committees, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NSF - Appropriate Technology, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NSF Cause Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation Regulations, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NSF Notices, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - New York Zoological Society, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - President's Letters, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fall Meeting College Arts & Sciences/Dentistry, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Energy and Environmental Studies at NYU, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Proposed PhD Program: Environmental Science & Energy, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Environmental Sciences Committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - UCLA Environmental Science & Engineering, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bight - General Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bight - Science Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Biology Dept - CVs, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - BIGHT - Proposals, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Biology Dept., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Research Advisory Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Research Policy Action, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Science, Technology and Human Values, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226299 1
  - New York University Controller's Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sterling Forest, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New York University Controller's Report, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New York University Controller's Report, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - NYU: Report of the Controller, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - A College Planning Cycle, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Operating Budget Request for the Fiscal Year 1979-1980 Five Year Development and Capital Plans for Arts and Science (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1970s Enrollment Statistics, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Workshop on Computer-Based Financial Planning Models CLAXTON, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1974-75 NYU Report, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226300 7
  - 1974-75 Higher Education Opportunities Program, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1972-73 Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1974-75 Legal Counsel Office, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - W.S. Budgets - Information, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1974-75 Budgets, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Heights Inventory, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1972-73 New Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1974-1975 Medical Center (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1974-75 University Newspapers, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1973-74 New York University Club, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting October 15, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Docket Joint Meeting of the Executive, Finance, and Buildings & Grounds Committees, Dec. 17 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NYU Minutes of a Joint Meeting of the Executive Committee, and the Buildings and Grounds Committee, Dec. 17 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting April 16, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting January 22 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Minutes of a Meeting of the Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees, March 12 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting October 20, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Minutes May 21 1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1973-1974 P.I.B./S.E.S. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Account Book, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Accounting, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Accounting, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Fund Rais. Info Systems, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - FAS Annual Report 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226301 5
  - Faculty vs. Staff, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tuition Remission, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Personnel, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Wash. Sq. Park Revisited, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Little Red Book: The Complete Street Guide to NYC, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Reprographic Services Handbook, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NYU Student Employment Handbook, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The New Executive Indemnity Plan, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Major Medical Insurance, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYU Charter and Bylaws, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NYU Charter and Bylaws July 1, 1956, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Planning for Effective Resource Allocation in Universities, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NYU Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School Adjustments to the "New Depression" in Higher Education, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYU Charter and Bylaws, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Governance of New York University, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Washington Square News (multiple copies), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - President Sawhill's Annual Message to the Faculties (multiple copies), undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report, May 31, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fiscal Review Group, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Higher Education Comprehensive Planning Program NY State, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - New York State Higher Education Space Inventory Report 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - New York State Higher Education Space Inventory Report 2, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - New York State Higher Education Space Inventory Report Fall 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Letter from TIAA Cref, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - New York University School of the Arts Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - New York University School of the Arts Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Washington Square News Report of Fiscal Review Group (multiple copies), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Report of the NYU Task Force on the Financial Emergency, May 19 1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - President Sawhill's Message to the Faculties Fall 1978 (multiple copies) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - NYU Office of Institutional Research Instructional Programs of NYU, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - The Hindle Committee Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226302 3
  - Staff Attrition Operations Analysis Study Final Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Salary Run Codes 101, 104, & 106 February 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Budget Manual, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NYU Goals Statement, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYU: The Goals Study of 1974, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Appendix: Goals Statements of the Schools and Colleges, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Interim Report of the All-University Commission on the Student Evaluation of Undergraduate Courses, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYU School of the Arts Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NYU University Education Quarterly Spring 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Official Statement Relating to $19,000,000 Dormitory Authority of State of NY, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Agreement: Dormitory Authority of the State of NY and NYU, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The Report of the NYU Task Force on the Financial Emergency, May 19 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Students and the Governance of NYU, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NYU Graduate School of Business Administration Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - The Hindle Committee Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NYU Education Quarterly: Teacher Behavior and Student Achievement, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - International Educational Exchange, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - AACRAO Fall 1976 Directory, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Handbook, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Notes/Budget, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Refunds, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Telephone Directory, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - GM The Changing Challenge, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - To Be Acted On, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NYU Official Directory, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Higher Education Prices and Price Indexes, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cooper Union, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Salary, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Snap Payload Dose, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Questionnaires, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dental Center - Funding, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Form 99, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226303 1
  - 1974-75 Naval Research Office, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1974-75 Pension Authorization, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1973-74 University Finances 1, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1973-74 University Finances 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal Review Group, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1974-75 Management Study Group, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Implementation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Coordinated Liberal Studies, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Budget, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - External Degree Program, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1972-1973 Faculty Club, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Form 99, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1974-75 Dental Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dental Center Phase Out, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1973-1974 Courant Institute (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1973-74 Finance Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1972-73 Dental School Report to Dr. Norman Mercer, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Budget Monitoring, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226304 9
  - Cost Allocation, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Auxiliaries, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Budget Preparation, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Burroughs, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Forms/Charts, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Key Codes, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Organization Charts, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Receipts/Invoices, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Reports Relating to Budgeting, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SEHNAP Budget Rpt., undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Student Affairs, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Tuition and Income - R. Hughs, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - VYDEC, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Xerox, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - CUNY, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Computer Accounts, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Computer Backup, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Enrollment Balance of Trade, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dental School, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - NYU Press Meeting, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SEHNAP Center for Field Research, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Payroll changes, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - School Comparison Studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Fiscal Review Material, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Financial Aid, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Financial Aid Mgt., undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - FAIDS, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Calendar, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Admissions, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Org. Charts, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Originals, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Admissions Data, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - SCAN Reports, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Budget Allocation, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1976/77 Section A, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1976/77 Section B, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1976/77 Section C, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1976/77 Appendix, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Plancode Notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Plancode Programs, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226305 6
  - Misc. Papers, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Attrition, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Attrition Quality of Life, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Budget, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda - Cost Allocation Procedure Review Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Minutes - Cost Allocation Procedure Review Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cost Accting, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Payroll System, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - ISI Memo, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Payroll Project, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Systems Diagrams, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Planning, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Budget Reviews, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Dental School, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ITEL Word Processor, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Brookdale Dental Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - S&D Dentistry, College of, Accreditation Report, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cooper Union, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Student Population - W. Payne, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - A - G Tenure File (Inactive), undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Carry Forward, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - School of Medicine Post-Graduate Medical School, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226306 4
  - Inactives Missing Tenure Cards, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - N - Z Tenure File (Inactive), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Budget Matters, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - H - M Tenure File (Inactive), undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Division of General Education, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Retailing, School of, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Law, School of, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Board of Review and Procedure for Hearings in Masters of Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Tenure: Council Action of March 22, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Tenure: Council Action of January 22, 1925, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Tenure: Senate Interpretations of January 13, 1949, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - University College of Arts and Sciences, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Faculty and Administration Lists, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226307 2
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Facts and Statistics, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Research B-1 Forms, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Tenure Stats, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Academic Freedom and Tenure Carry Forward, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - PER Appointments, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wolfe, Robert D., undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Weisband, Edward (Dr.), undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Polinger, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mason, Evelyn, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - New York University Proposed School of Nursing, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Bromberg Files, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Bromberg Files - Misc. Administrative, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bromberg Files - Central Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226308 0
  - Bromberg Files - FAS, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Bromberg Files - FBA, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bromberg Files - CIMS, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bromberg Files - School of Ed., School of Eng. And Sci., GPA Grad School of Social Work, School of Law, Library, School of Medicine, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bromberg Files - School of Arts, FBA, Central Admin., Dentistry, School of Ed., Misc., 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bromberg Files - FAS, CIMS, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bromberg Files - Gallatin, GPA, Grad. School of Social Work, IFA, Law, Library, School of Med., 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Bromberg Files - FAS, CIMS, School of the Arts, CA, Dentistry, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Administrative, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Correspondence Prepared for the Pres., 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bromberg Files - Letters of Resignation, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bromberg Files - Professors Emeriti, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bromberg Files - Faculty of the School of the Arts, Athletics, Int. Studies, SCE, Dentistry, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226309 8
  - Bromberg Chronological, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bromberg Chronological, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Education, Commission On, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Report on the Restructuring of Counseling Services, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Minutes, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Users Manual NYU Employee Data Base Report Request, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square College, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Research B-1 Forms, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Budget Matters, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Division of Athletics, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226310 6
  - Budget Matters, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Code 101 Blue Sheets, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Code 101 Blue Sheets, 1962-1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Docket - Board of Trustees Meetings, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Overage Lists, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Overage Lists, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Budget Matters, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Budget Matters, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Research Recommendations, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Research Recommendations, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Budget Matters, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Research Recommendations, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Research Recommendations, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Budget Matters, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Research B-1 Forms, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Faculty and Administration Lists, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Faculty and Administration Lists, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Unemployment Insurance, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226311 4
  - Terman Engineering, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Student Senate and University Senate U. Heights Center, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Engineering Department, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Tel Aviv University, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Teachers and Writers Collaborative, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - School of the Arts, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Teachers for a Democratic Society, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Teachers for a Democratic Society, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - State Education Dept., 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry, College of, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Commerce, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Education, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Engineering & Science, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Student Affairs (Wsq.), 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Courant Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Courant Institute, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Workshops, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Tuition Increase, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Troy State University, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - E.R. Tichauer Medical Center, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - UCAR, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - GPA, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - GBA (2), 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - GBA, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Time Reports, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Law, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 28)